[Music]
Hello friends welcome back to welcome
and here I am back with another exciting
video and the stock we're going to
discuss today is ICICI lumbar General
Insurance company
so as most of you must be knowing it is
a general insurance company which is
primarily dealing with General insurance
reinsurance insurance claims and many
other interest related work so this
company was I think
stock market listed in 2017 and from 680
levels it has come to 267 in the last
five to five and a half years
so it's a huge company coming from ICICI
Bank organization and if you look at a
one-year chart the stock has kind of
stared at this like almost dropped by
you can say 11 percent and but has gone
down to a levels of almost 1100 and now
it has gone back to 1267.
so and it has a p of 39.72 100.72
so what we're going to discuss today is
the technical analysis and we'll see
whether this talk can go back to its
like earlier highs up close to 1400 plus
and if yes what is that direction and
whether you should buy the stock right
now all right so for that let me take
you to the pipe pressure terminal
so in the fireplace that the stock has
been recommended as you can see um the
stock and the rationalize the stock has
retaken this 200-day moving average
which is this green line and it has
crossed that with heavy volumes and on
today that is third of January the stock
has moved up from that level so you can
buy the stock in the range of 272 to 288
right now it is close to 270 so you can
buy this stock tomorrow and you can
expect
um
Target price of close to 1440 which is
almost 13 percent off from here so this
being a good company and obviously the
technicals look good and as I said
earlier it is end up almost dropped 11
percent in last one year so there is a
potential of this stock crossing the
1400 levels but obviously one thing to
keep in mind is keep track of this stop
loss and and in the earlier videos I've
said like for some companies suggest
that even if it goes below the stop plus
you can buy on to the ads one of the
examples being better than the limited I
made a video for that yesterday so it's
ICS sale number is not that kind of
stock so if goes below stop plus you
start to sell and get out of it but if
you're invest in a company like vedanta
you can keep on adding to the stock
every time there is a decline so because
you will be getting good dividend
so that's pretty much it I hope you like
this video if yes give it a thumbs up
and if you're new to the channel do not
forget to subscribe to the channel
thanks a lot for watching